dear customer i am an icici bank
representative and i am going to take
you through an incredibly easy journey
of video kyc for your personal loan so
let's begin
login with the link which you have
received for video kyc on both sms and
email
before you open the link please ensure
that you are in a strong network area or
have a good wifi connectivity on your
device also follow a few instructions
for smooth process
keep original pan card a blank paper and
a black pen for signature along with you
while doing the video kyc
look into the camera while verifying the
details
while capturing the photo make sure
you're in a proper attire with white
background proper lighting and keep your
eyes open
do not show aadhar card or share your
aadhar number during the call
also no third person should be visible
or audible during the call
now once you have opened the link you
will get an otp through a sms and an
email to login to the video kyc portal
after entering the otp please click on
login then you will see a video kyc
option click on the same to initiate the
video kyc call after this you will see a
pop-up with video kyc instructions click
on ok
the next screen will show you your name
and your pan number you will need to
enter your aadhaar number and accept the
terms and conditions
then click on verify now only once and
wait for the aadhaar otp to be received
on your aadhaar linked mobile number
please avoid multiple clicks and ensure
that the mobile number linked to aadhar
is active as you will receive an otp
triggered by ui dai on it enter the otp
and click on continue
then your aadhaar photo and address will
be fetched from uidai please confirm
that your address details and current
address as per the application form are
correct by ticking after confirmation
you need to click on initiate video kyc
button only once and wait for the web
page to load please avoid multiple
clicks
after initiation the system will connect
you to an agent request you to wait till
you connect to the agent
when you are connected to the agent you
will see a chat window and the agent
will initiate a two-way video call
please accept it
when the video call starts the agent
will ask you to share your location and
other verification parameters
please note that you need to be in india
while initiating video kyc
the agent will guide you through the
rest of the process and that is your
video kyc journey
yes it's as simple as that with icici
bank